Tallulah Shepherd

USER, PROGRAMMER, DESIGNER

Details

Minneapolis, MN.

+13104904954

tallulahshepherd@gmail.com

Links

tallulahshepherd.com

LinkedIn

Skills

Adobe Creative Suite

UX Design

Game Design

Figma

Unity3D

Unreal Engine

Java

Python

C++

Slack

Google Suite

Android Studio

Graphic Design

HTML & CSS

Hobbies

Video games Fantasy books Superhero movies Watercolor painting

Profile

Designer and software developer with a wide range of technical *and* artistic experience. I bring empathy and a human element into everything I make, along with a strong **drive for results** and proven ability to learn **quickly** and **enthusiastically**.

Employment History

LEAD RETAIL SUBJECT MATTER EXPERT, Apple, Inc, Retail Contact Center

FEBRUARY 2021 - PRESENT

Was promoted into the **Lead position** for all Retail Subject Matter Experts in Apple's Retail Contact Center. Continued to drive team engagement on a larger scale, as well as having more room to address areas of growth and become a reliable resource for experts and specialists.

SUBJECT MATTER EXPERT, Apple, Inc, Retail Contact Center

NOVEMBER 2020 - FEBRUARY 2021

Pivoted to Apple's Retail Contact Center during the COVID-19 pandemic, where I started as a Chat Support Specialist and was quickly promoted into a Subject Matter Expert due to my product knowledge, comfort with ambiguity, and commitment to helping my team succeed.

SPECIALIST, Apple, Inc., Minnetonka, MN

OCTOBER 2019 - PRESENT

Uncovered customer needs, built personalized solutions, while being a resource on all technology use within the store. Flexed into other roles to support the store: taking tech appointments; maintained visuals; assisted operations team.

DESIGNER & DEVELOPER, Freelance, WI & MN

MARCH 2018 - JULY 2019

Built websites, applications and several different graphic proposals, primarily in the Wisconsin area.

DATA TEAM INTERN, Beloit College, Beloit, WI

SEPTEMBER 2015 - APRIL 2019

Used **Python** and **Raisers Edge** to digitalize the College's paper records, where I later manipulated, sorted, and visualized the data.

Education

COMPUTER SCIENCE, Beloit College, Beloit

AUGUST 2015 - MAY 2019

References

References available upon request